Guide to the Barrett Gallagher photographs and film, 1932-1989
Gallagher, Barrett photographs and film, 1932-1989
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Barrett Gallagher photographs and film, 1932-1989
3956
Barrett L. Gallagher, 1913-1994
92 cubic ft.
Photographs, negatives, contact prints, photographic enlargements, 16mm film
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Photographs of Cornell University faculty and campus scenes taken by Barrett Gallagher include Alexander M. Drummond; University President Livingston Farrand and his wife, Daisy; University Presidents Deane W. Malott and Frank H.T. Rhodes; arts quadrangle buildings, museum, and other photographs for publications such as the Cornell Alumni News. Also, 16mm film Spring in Ithaca, ca. 1960.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University Class of 1936. Barrett Gallagher was a professional photographer and his work includes photographs of World War II action in the Pacific as well as a wide range of assignments for Fortune, Life, and other magazines. Gallagher also photographed politicians, musicians, and performers including Nelson Rockefeller, Carl Sagan, Ingrid Bergman, Leonard Bernstein, Mitch Miller, Burgess Meredith, Isaac Stern, Yehudi Menuhin, the John Kirby Sextet, Stuff Smith, and Cozy Cole.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Photographs, negatives, contact prints, and selected enlargements; photographs of Cornell University faculty and campus scenes taken by Barrett Gallagher. Subjects include Alexander M. Drummond; University President Livingston Farrand and his wife, Daisy; University Presidents Deane W. Malott and Frank H.T. Rhodes; and arts quadrangle buildings. Also, 16mm film "Spring in Ithaca," c. 1960.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gallagher, Barrett L., 1913-1994.; Drummond, Alexander M.; Farrand, Margaret Carleton.; Farrand, Livingston, 1867-1939.; Malott, Deane W. (Deane Waldo), 1898-; Rhodes, Frank Harold Trevor.; Cornell University--Pictorial works.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Except for Boxes 1, 2, and 44, whose contents are itemized, the notes on the contents of the boxes is not exhaustive but rather simply indicative of the types of photographs contained within.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Prints, Cornell Related
Boxes 1-2, 76, 118-119, 121, 164, 166
Series II. Motion Picture Film
Box 3
Series III. Negatives
Boxes 4-36
Series IV. Contact Prints
Boxes 37-53
Series V. Slides
Boxes 54-75
Series VI. Prints
Boxes 76-170
Series VII. Color Transparencies, Tear Sheets and Magazine Covers
Boxes 171-174
Series VIII. Texts, Papers
Boxes 175-177
Series IX. Oversize Prints
Boxes 178-195
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Prints, Cornell Related
  - Alexander Drummond (1934) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alexander Drummond (1932) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Goldwyn Smith Hall (1934) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Livingston Farrand (1934) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Livingston Farrand (1934) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Livingston Farrand (1934) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Daisy Farrand (1936) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Daisy Farrand (1936) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Daisy Farrand (1937) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt and Flora Rose (1934) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Norman Moore (1934) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Norman Moore (1934) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dexter Kimball (1936) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - William Hagan (1936) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Herman Diedrichs (1936) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Herman Diedrichs (1936) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Herman Diedrichs (1936) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cornelius Betten (1936) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Floyd Richtmyer (1936) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Floyd Richtmyer (1936) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - George Young (1935) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Carl Ladd (1936) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Carl Ladd (1936) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Carl Ladd (1935) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Robert Ogden (1935) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Robert Ogden (1935) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Charles Burdick (1936) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Charles Burdick (1936) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Charles Burdick (1936) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Jim Wray (1932) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Dean Malott (1951) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Dean Malott (1951) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Eileen Gallagher (1936) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Arts Quad (1936) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Willard Straight Hall (1936) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Alexander Drummond (1947) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Alexander Drummond (1947) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Frank Rhodes Inauguration (1977) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Frank Rhodes Inauguration (1977) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Arthur Bloom - Enfield Glen (1977) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - James Mason (1935) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Louis Boochever (1934) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Harry Caplan (1934) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Halladay Underwood (1934) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Olaf Brauner (1934) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Livingston Farrand (1934) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Livingston Farrand (1934) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Arts Quad (1934) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - George Young Jr. (1935) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - George Young Jr. (1935) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Wilder Dwight Bancroft (1934) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Edward Whiting (1934) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Foster Coffin (1934) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Foster Coffin (1934) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lane Cooper (1934) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Woodford Patterson (1934) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Harry Caplan (1934) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Harry Weld (1934) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Harley Howe (1934) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Robert Sibley (1934) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Charles Durham (1934) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mynderse Van Cleef (1934) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Morrill Hall (1934) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Freshman-Sophomore Fracas (1934) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Spring Day Duck Race (1934) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Winter Scene (1934) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Winter Scene (1934) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Winter Scene (1934) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Ernest Merritt (1934) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - George Rogalsky (1934) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Arthur Browne (1934) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Foster Coffin (1934) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Anna Grace (1934) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Alexander Drummond (1934) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Woodford Patterson (1933) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Lane Cooper (1934) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Jim Wray (1934) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Series II. Motion Picture Film
  - Movie Film - Springtime In Ithaca, F-2311; 35mm; USE COPY (VHS) V-51 (Box 3)
- Series III. Negatives
  - Negatives (1934-1970), Alexander Drummond Betty Dick Dumont T.V. 1948 Farrands Ground Breaking For Performing Arts Center Leonard Bernstein Republic Aircraft Presentation Showgirls And Costumes 1948 Snowy Owl (Box 4)
  - Negatives (1936 - 1942) (Box 5)
  - Negatives (1942 - 1948) (Box 6)
  - Negatives (1949 - 1954) (Box 7)
  - Rolleiflex Negatives (1936 - 1945) (Box 8)
  - Negatives (1938 - 1968), Babson Map Balloons Nelson Rockefeller World War II (Box 9)
  - Negatives, Linhof B&W Kodachrome (Box 10)
  - Negatives (Jan 1946, Jan-Feb 1947) (Box 11)
  - Negatives (Mar - Dec 1947) (Box 12)
  - Negatives (1948) (Box 13)
  - Negatives (1949 - Dec 1950) (Box 14)
  - Negatives (Aug 1950 - Dec 1951) (Box 15)
  - Negatives (Jan 1952 - Jun 1953) (Box 16)
  - Negatives (Jul 1953) (Box 17)
  - Negatives (Oct 22, 1950 - Jun 10, 1954) (Box 18)
  - Negatives From Hoffman K&L Lab (Mar 1955 - Jun 26, 1959) (Box 19)
  - Negatives From Hoffman K&L Lab (Mar 7, 1960 - Dec 1, 1961) (Box 20)
  - Negatives From Hoffman K&L Lab (Dec 1, 1961 - Feb 3, 1966) (Box 21)
  - Negatives From Hoffman K&L Lab (Apr 1966 - Jul 1977) (Box 22)
  - Negatives (Jun 22, 1954 - Mar 31, 1956) (Box 23)
  - Negatives (Mar 19, 1956 - Jul 17, 1957) (Box 24)
  - Negatives (Sep 1, 1957 - May 20, 1959) (Box 25)
  - Negatives (Jun 4, 1959 - Mar 30, 1961) (Box 26)
  - Negatives (Apr 1, 1961 - Dec 29, 1962) (Box 27)
  - Negatives (Jan 7, 1963 - Sep 27, 1964) (Box 28)
  - Negatives (Oct 1, 1964 - Apr 11, 1967) (Box 29)
  - Negatives (Apr 11, 1967 - Aug 31, 1970) (Box 30)
  - Negatives (Sep 1, 1970 - Mar 28, 1972) (Box 31)
  - Negatives (Mar 28, 1972 - Dec 1975) (Box 32)
  - Negatives (Jan 1976 - Feb 1980) (Box 33)
  - Negatives (Mar 1980 - Jan 21, 1987) (Box 34)
  - Negatives (May 25, 1987 - Oct 29, 1990) (Box 35)
  - Negatives (1971 - 1972), East Africa (Box 36)
- Series IV. Contact Prints
  - Contact Prints (Up To 1947) (Box 37)
  - Contact Prints (1948 - 1950) (Box 38)
  - Contact Prints (Oct 1950 - Jan 1959), Navy (Box 39)
  - Contact Prints (1953 - Dec 1954), Korea (Box 40)
  - Contact Prints (Jan 1955 - May 1957) (Box 41)
  - Contact Prints (1956 - 1957), Sixth Fleet and Strikeback (Box 42)
  - Contact Prints (Jun 1957 - Sep 1960) (Box 43)
  - Contact Prints (Oct 1960 - May 1961), Cornell: (Box 44)
    - Engineering Library, Carpenter Hall, 01-02-14
    - Library Tower, new Olin Library at right, 01-15-23
    - Sage chapel, 01-24-34
    - Statler Hall, Hotel School and Inn, 02-02-05
    - New engineering quad, Carpenter Hall, 02-06-08
    - Anabel Taylor Hall - interfaith building, 02-09-11
    - Carpenter Hall, engineering administration, 02-12
    - Engineering quad, Hollister in foreground, 02-13-26
    - Chapel, Anabel Taylor Hall, 02-27-33
    - The Law School - Myron Taylor Hall, 02-34-37
    - Engineering quad, lake, Anabel Taylor, Library tower, 03-01-32
    - Perry W. Gilbert, Prof. Zoology (sharks), 03-34-37
    - Perry W. Gilbert, Prof. Zoology (sharks), 04-02-20
    - Zoology lab - salamander dissection, 04-21-37
    - Zoology lab - salamander dissection, 05-02-12
    - Triphammer Falls, Beebe Lake, 05-13-23
    - One of the new engineering buildings, 05-26-27
    - Class in engineering, 05-28-36
    - Prof. John R. Moynihan, Engineering Mechanics and Materials, 06-02-04
    - Materials Testing bay, Kimball-Thurson Hall, 06-05-13
    - Student J.L. Ajmani, loading beam, 06-14-19
    - Prof. and student, 06-20-23
    - Main lecture room, Electrical Engineering, Phillips Hall, 06-24-26
    - Model of Puerto Rico Radio, Physics and Space Center. White shirt, Prof. William H. Erickson, Asst. Director, School of Electrical Engineering In coat, Research Assoc. H.J. Eckelmann., 06-27-37
    - Microwave Lab, 07-02-07
    - Prof. and class, Electrical Engineering, 07-08-10
    - Electrical Engineering office, 07-11-14
    - Electronics lab, Electrical Engineering, 07-15-18
    - Prof. William H. Erickson, Assistant Director, School of Electrical Engineering, 07-19-21
    - Engineering Physics, graduate student Schwaebel, 07-22-28
    - Engineering Physics, ultrahigh vacuum electron diffraction camera for surface study of copper oxidation, 07-30-32
    - Main quad, 08-02-06
    - Prof. George H. Healey, Curator, Rare Books, lecture on Christopher Marlowe, 08-07-36
    - Prof. George H. Healey showing one of three extant original copies of Marlowe's Tamerlane, 09-02-17
    - Prof. Harry Caplan, Classics, Greek, 09-18-24
    - Engineering Materials Research, high pressure, 09-25-32
    - Hydraulics lab, Civil Engineering, 09-33-37
    - Hydraulics lab, Civil Engineering, 10-02-05
    - Assistant Dean of Engineering, John F. McManus, striped tie, 10-06-14
    - Break up of stream of water under strobe light, 10-15-36
    - Thermal engineering lab, 11-02-14
    - Aeronautical Engineering, Upson Hall, shock tube installation, 11-15-27
    - Engineering class - seminar, Upson Hall, 11-28-32
    - Machine Design section, Upson Hall, 11-33-36
    - Julliard String Quartet, Statler Auditorium, 12-03-07
    - President Deane W. Malott, 12-08-28
    - John Summerskill, Vice President for Student Affairs, 13-01-20
    - John E. Burton, Vice President for Business, 13-21-36
    - Zoology lab, 14-02-18
    - Willard Straight Cafeteria (Student Union), 14-19-22
    - Willard Straight Hi-Fi room, 14-19-22
    - New Olin library under construction, 14-27-30
    - Andrew D. White's library, preserved in main library, 14-31-33
    - Andrew D. White's library, preserved in main library, 15-13-21
    - Main library reading room, 15-22-37
    - Main library reading room, 16-02-06
    - New Olin library under construction, 16-07-09
    - Museum of casts, Goldwin Smith Hall (Arts and Sciences), 16-10-26
    - Architecture library, Sibley Dome, 16-27-29
    - Architecture library, Drafting room, 16-33-36
    - Architecture - drafting rooms, models, exhibits (Sibley Hall), 17-01-33
    - Freshman drafting room, 17-34-35
    - Freshman drafting room, 18-02-07
    - Architecture drafting rooms, 18-08-14
    - Graduate students, Architecture, 18-15-21
    - Andrew D. White Museum of Art - Tibetan robe, 18-22-37
    - New York State Veterinary College - operation on bull for "corns", 19-02-33
    - Frank Gannett Medical Clinic for students, 19-34-36
    - Anabel Taylor Hall building for interfaith, 19-37
    - New York State Veterinary College - operation on bull for "corns", 20-01-10
    - Anabel Taylor Hall interfaith, 20-11-14
    - Gannett Clinic, X-ray. Dr. E.C. Showacre, 20-15-22
    - Gannett Clinic, Dr. C.D. Darling, Clinical and Preventive Medicine, 20-23-25
    - Gannett Clinic, reception and records, 20-26-37
    - Gannett Clinic, reception and records, 21-02-17
    - Gannett Clinic, specialty waiting room, 21-18-21
    - Gannett Clinic, doctors' offices, 21-22-37
    - Library slope - original buildings Morrill and McGraw (with tower), 22-01-08
    - Museum of political memorabilia - Mann lib., Agriculture, 22-09-34
    - New York State College of Agriculture, Dr. F.C. Steward, Professor of Botany, studying grown of carrot tissue, 23-01-15
    - Dr. Steward and graduate students, chromatagram, 23-16-34
    - Dr. F.C. Steward, Botany, 24-02-08
    - Fraternity house, 24-09-12
    - Dr. Norman S. Moore, Director, Clinic and Infirmary, 24-13-19
    - Cornell Infirmary, Dr. Moore and students, 24-20-37
    - Cornell Dramatic Club, University Theatre, Willard Straight, 25-08-11
    - Hunt Bradley, General Alumni Secretary, 25-12-19
    - Noyes Lodge on Beebe Lake, 25-20-36
    - John Mason Potter, News Bureau, 25-37
    - John Mason Potter, News Bureau, 26-01-05
    - Ornithology lab, Sapsucker Woods. Arthur A. Allen, Professor Emeritus, honorary director (shirtsleeves). Professor Paul P. Kellogg, Ornithology (black coat, white hair), the bird-recording experts., 26-06-35
    - Professor Henry A. Detweiler, Assistant Dean, Architecture. Popular slide lecture on European Architecture for non-architects., 27-02-27
    - Professor Hans A. Bethe, Physics, in office, 28-02-13
    - Professor Hans A. Bethe, Physics, in synchrotron - Newman Lab, 28-14-24
    - Crew tanks, Teagle Hall, Coach "Stork" Sanford, 29-02-33
    - Olympic Pool, Teagle, 29-34-36
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Professor M.F. Newfeld, 30-01-13
    - Madame Frances Perkins, Visiting Lecturer, Industrial and Labor Relations, 30-15
    - The Law School, Professor Rudolph B. Schlessinger, 30-22-35
    - Peewee hockey - Lynah Hall (Saturday morning, town and gown), 31-01-27
    - Alumni office meeting, 32-01-12
    - Professor Clinton Rossiter, Government, 32-13-23
    - Main quad original buildings, 32-24-27
    - Professor Clinton Rossiter, Government, 33-02-28
    - One World Meeting, Anabel Taylor Hall, 33-29-37
    - Sage Chapel, nondenominational, 34-28-36
    - Heptagonal Track Meet, Barton Hall. Annual event, only a remote campus can attract sufficient crowds, 35-26-34
    - Cornell Council Meeting, Willard Straight Annual Report, 36-20-35
    - Trustees meeting, 37-02-16
    - Provost Sanford S. Atwood, 37-17-24
    - Vice President J.L. Zwingle, 37-25-32
    - Vice President Theodore Wright (now retired), 37-33-37
    - Vice President Theodore Wright, now retired, 38-01-04
    - Collyer Boat House, Cayuga Lake inlet, 38-05-21
    - Crews on inlet, 38-22-24
    - Taughannock Falls, 38-25-29
    - Cornell University Medical College - Dr. Pap (George Papanicolaou) with his wife and assistants, 39-02-36
    - Dr. Walter Modell, Pharmacology. Penicillin lecture., 40-03-27
    - Dr. E.C. Richardson, Surgery. Sophomore lab on retina, 40-28-37
    - Dr. Pap (George Papanicolaou), 41-01-13
    - Clinical Pathological Conference, Auditorium, 41-14-29
    - Clinical Pathological Conference, Auditorium, 42-02-24
    - The Cornell University-New York Hospital School of Nursing, 42-25-37
    - Student nurse aspirating patient, 43-01-03
    - Nursing - lecture on electrical conductivity, 43-04-14
    - School of Nursing, 43-15-34
    - Medical College, Dr. Vincent duVigneaud, Biochemistry (Nobel Prize), 44-08-36
    - Medical College, Lab, Biochemistry, 45-01-17
    - Plastic Surgery, Dr. Herbert Conway with Residents completing ten years of graduate study, 45-18-27
    - Cornell College-The New York Hospital-Cornell Medical Center, New York City, 46-00-24
    - Enfield Glen, 47-02-36
    - Enfield Glen, 48-01-34
    - Enfield Glen, 49-01-14
    - Buttermilk Falls, 49-15-21
    - Ezra Cornell statue, main quad, 49-22-32
    - Cornell Co-op, Campus store, 49-33-36
    - Gannett Clinic, 50-51-37
    - Gannett Clinic, 51-02-12
    - Gannett Clinic entrance, 51-13-17
    - Willard Straight Hall, the Student Union, 51-18-30
    - Students, 52-01-36
    - Students, 53-01-37
    - Indian student, 54-02-07
    - Back of Gannett Clinic, 54-08-28
    - Editorial rooms, Cornell Daily Sun, 54-29-33
    - Managing editor of Cornell Daily Sun pulls proof at 2 A.M. The student-run Sun is Ithaca's only morning paper., 54-34-37
    - Professor Damon Boynton, Pomology, Dean of Graduate School, 55-01-10
    - Professor A.M. Srb (sic) with graduate student, genetic research lab, plant breeding, 55-11-19
    - Research Associate Dr. S.S. Kwong, Pomology, 55-20-22
    - Graduate Student Frank Denis, Pomology, 55-23-25
    - Wiegand Herbarium, Professor R.T. Clausen, curator, and graduate student, 56-02-12
    - The Graduate School of Nutrition, determining patient's specific gravity, 56-13-24
    - Agricultural quadrangle, 56-27-32
    - Main quadrangle, A.D. White's statue, 57-01-07
    - Men's dorms, Baker, 57-08-11
    - Goldwin Smith Hall, Arts and Sciences, 57-13-15
    - Dean Damon Boynton, Graduate School, with graduate students, 57-16-27
    - Korean graduate student at controls of synchrotron, Nuclear Physics, Newman lab, 57-28-29
    - Synchrotron Detector room, 57-31-35
    - Korean graduate student at synchrotron control, 58-02-06
    - Graduate student and small synchrotron, 58-07-29
    - Craft shop, Willard Straight Hall, 59-02-09
    - Crews on inlet, 59-10-30
    - New York State College of Home Economics, Professor C.J. Personius, Head, Food and Nutrition, University Trustee, 60-01-17
    - Design and House Planning, 60-18-34
    - Research lab, 60-35-37
    - Laboratory, Home Economics, 61-01-19
    - Slide lecture on architecture of Europe, 61-20-27
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Professor W.F. Whyte, communications table requires students to go through channels, 61-28-37
    - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Professor W.F. Whyte, communications table requires students to go through channels, 62-01-12
    - The Law School - library, 62-13-20
    - Anabel Taylor Hall and library tower, 62-21-27
    - Law library, 62-28-29
    - Moot Court, 62-30-37
    - The Law School, Moot Court, 63-02-10
    - Liberian Law student, 63-11-16
    - Greek Law student, 63-14-19
    - Professor Peter Olafson, Pathology, Veterinary, 63-20-35
    - Frosh La Crosse, Cornell vs. Hobart, 64-01-07
    - Professor M.H. Abrams, English, 64-12-34
    - Frosh La Crosse, Cornell vs. Hobart, 65-01-17
    - Home Economics, Interior Design, 65-18-27
    - Carrel in Mann library, Agriculture, 65-29-35
    - New York State College of Home Economics, Crease Recovery Test, 66-02-08
    - New York State College of Home Economics, Design, 66-09-34
    - Class on the grass, near Home Economics, 67-01-13
    - Catalogue Room, Mann library (Agriculture), 67-14-22
    - Reading Room, Mann library, 67-23-27
    - Catalogue room, Mann library, 67-28-31
    - Reference room, Mann library, 67-32-37
    - Main Quadrangle, 68-01-18
    - Kappa Alpha Fraternity, 68-19-24
    - Classes on grass, main quad, 69-01-12
    - Goldwin Smith Hall, Arts and Sciences, 69-13-18
    - Professor K.L. Turk, Agriculture, Head of Animal Husbandry, 69-19-36
    - Gardening class, Professor A.J. Pratt, Vegetable Crops, Agriculture, 70-01-20
    - Agriculture - Ecology and Insect Pathology, 70-21-37
    - Agriculture - Ecology and Insect Pathology, 71-01-32
    - Inorganic Chemistry Lab, Baker, Arts and Sciences, 72-01-11
    - Ray spectrometer, 72-12-14
    - ROTC - Annual President's Review, 72-15-32
    - ROTC Review - Army, Navy, Air Force, 73-01-17
    - The School of Education, Graduate Student Teacher Deborah Shea teaching World War II History in Boynton Junior High School in downtown Ithaca, 73-18-34
    - Professor Emeritus Alexis L. Romanoff (the Egg Man), 74-01-27
    - The Graduate School of Business and Public Administration, Professor Earl Brooks and seminar, 75-02-20
    - Library, McGraw Hall, 75-21-25
    - Geology Field Trip, looking for an interglacial gorge, 75-26-37
    - Triphammer bridge between campus, women's dorms, fraternities, 76-01-10
    - Geology Field Trip on campus, by Triphammer Falls, 76-11-37
    - Professor M.G. de Chazeus, Business and Public Administration, 77-01-20
    - The School of Hotel Administration, 77-21-36
    - The School of Hotel Administration, 78-01-32
    - Models, Architecture, 79-01-11
    - Crew Race on Cayuga Lake. Cornell won all races, 79-13-36
    - Crew Race on Cayuga Lake, 80-01-18
    - Professor Thomas Gold, Astronomy, Space Research, 80-19-34
    - Crew races, Cornell won all, 81-01-23
    - Professor Thomas Gold (Nobel Prize), 81-24-36
    - Student orchestra concert on library slope, 82-02-37
    - New Olin Library for graduate study, 83-02-37
    - Treasurer Lewis H. Durland, 84-01-22
    - Library tower and new Olin library, 84-23-34
    - Ezra Cornell statue, 84-35-36
    - Ezra Cornell statue, 85-01-12
    - Professor A.R. Holmberg, Anthropology, Peru expert, 85-13-33
    - Professor J.M. Echols, Linguistics, Far Eastern Studies, 86-01-18
    - Professor Henry Elder, Architecture, 86-19-37
    - Professor Henry Elder, Architecture, 87-01-06
    - Main Reading Room, Olin library, 87-07-11
    - Library tower, Olin library, Ezra Day Hall, 87-12-29
    - Seminar, Professor Henry Guerlac, History of Science, 88-01-16
    - Industrial and Labor Relations, Professor W.F. Whyte, leadership and teamwork experiment, 88-17-26
    - Construction of new buildings for Industrial and Labor Relations, 88-27-35
    - Industrial and Labor Relations experiment, leadership and teamwork. Professor W.H. Whyte. Number 8913, Copyright Fortune Magazine, 1961, 89-01-35
    - Seminar, Assistant Professor Andrew Hacker, Government, 90-01-24
    - Indian graduate student, Agriculture, in Mann library catalogue room, 90-25-35
    - Indian graduate student, Agriculture, 91-01-18
    - Dean of Architecture Burnham Kelly (grey coat) and Director of Budge Paul L. McKeegan, 91-19-35
    - Library tower, Olin library, Ezra Day Hall, 92-02-23
    - Professor Richard Bradfield, Agronomy, Agriculture, 92-24-35
    - Professor Richard Bradfield, Agronomy, Agriculture, 93-02-28
    - University heating plant boilers, 93-29-37
    - University heating plant boilers, 94-01-05
    - The late Professor S.E. Whicher, English, 94-06-36
    - Library tower, Olin library, Ezra Day Hall, 95-01-23
    - Student Government Executive Board, 95-24-34
    - Andrew D. White statue, 96-01-14
    - Oral exam for Ph.D. in German, 96-27-36
    - Chemistry graduate student instructs in quantitative analysis, 97-05-15
    - Chemistry graduate student, research, running a "shock", 97-17-28
    - Professor Hazel M. Hauck, Emeritus, Food and Nutrition, 97-29-35
    - Professor Hazel M. Hauck (African expert), 98-01-09